openfilesnow.com 2011-05-25

# Privacy Policy | Open, View, Edit And Fix Any File !

## **Privacy Policy for OpenFilesNow.com**

**OpenFilesNow.com**  respects the privacy of all its users and is committed to protecting such privacy in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy explains **OpenFilesNow.com**  treatment of your personally identifiable information collected in connection with your activities on the OpenFilesNow.com web site.

**1\. COLLECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

**OpenFilesNow.com** will not collect or use any information about the visitors to the Web Site and your visit to the Web Site is anonymous. The only exception is when we will need information that personally identifies in order to fulfill a contractual obligation towards you pursuant to what is set forth in section 2 below.

**2\. CONTRACTUAL OBLIGATION**

If you make a purchase from **OpenFilesNow.com** , you will be asked to provide your name, email and payment information. We may use information collected in the following ways:

   1\. To process, validate and verify purchases.  
   2\. To contact you to reconfirm or verify accuracy of information provided.  
   3\. To register you as a customer.  
   4\. To open and maintain a support account for you.  
   5\. To send email notifications about new, existing, enhanced products or services.  
   6\. To send information on special offers, or to obtain your feedback to help enhance existing features or provide added products and services.  
   7\. To enable us to personalize content, advertising and promotions based on preferences, needs, suggestions, or recommendations.  
   8\. To provide advance notice of termination of a trial period or an opportunity to extend a trial period, or advance notice of expiration of your software license.  

We may disclose and use personally identifiable information in special circumstances where it is necessary to enforce our service agreements or terms of use (for example protect our intellectual property rights), and your compliance with the applicable End User License Agreement(s) contained within the PC Health Advisor software. We may also disclose or use your personal information when we, in good faith, believe that the applicable law may require us to do so.

The information you provide will not be used for any other commercial purposes and will not be sold, rented, leased or otherwise forwarded to any third party with the exception of our sales processor RevenueWire, who will process your orders and distribute the goods or services that you have requested.

**3\. THE USE OF COOKIES**

OpenFilesNow.com does use "cookies" for the sole purpose of tracking affiliate referrals and conversion. We do not save any personally identifiable information in cookies sent to your browser. Cookies are identifiers that a web site can send to your browser to keep on your computer to facilitate your next visit to the site. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many web sites use them. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. All parts of our website will function correctly if you disable cookies.

**4\. LINKS TO OTHER SITES**

The Web Site may contain links to other web sites. **OpenFilesNow.com** does not monitor or control the content of such web sites or whether such web sites collect or process your personal data. Accordingly, **OpenFilesNow.com** assumes no responsibility or liability whatsoever for any kind of material available at such sites and recommends that you review the separate privacy policies of such sites.

**5\. CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**

**OpenFilesNow.com** may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. Any changes will be posted to this site, so we encourage you to continuously review our Privacy Policy.

**6\. CONTACT INFORMATION**

For questions regarding this Privacy Policy please Contact Us.

**7\. OPT OUT INSTRUCTIONS**

To opt out of any communications from this website, please send an email through our Contact Form.
